{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20wrote%20the%20novel%20'Pride%20and%20Prejudice'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jane%20Austen",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Charlotte%20Bronte",
        "Emily%20Dickinson",
        "Louisa%20May%20Alcott"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20author%20wrote%20the%20play%20'Macbeth'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "William%20Shakespeare",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Christopher%20Marlowe",
        "Thomas%20Middleton",
        "Ben%20Jonson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20author%20of%20the%20novel%20'1984'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "George%20Orwell",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Aldous%20Huxley",
        "Ray%20Bradbury",
        "Kurt%20Vonnegut"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20wrote%20the%20book%20'To%20Kill%20a%20Mockingbird'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Harper%20Lee",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mark%20Twain",
        "John%20Steinbeck",
        "F.%20Scott%20Fitzgerald"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20author%20wrote%20the%20poem%20'The%20Raven'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Edgar%20Allan%20Poe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Walt%20Whitman",
        "Ralph%20Waldo%20Emerson",
        "Emily%20Dickinson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20wrote%20the%20book%20'Frankenstein'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mary%20Shelley",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bram%20Stoker",
        "H.G.%20Wells",
        "Robert%20Louis%20Stevenson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20author%20is%20known%20for%20writing%20'The%20Adventures%20of%20Huckleberry%20Finn'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mark%20Twain",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Charles%20Dickens",
        "Herman%20Melville",
        "Nathaniel%20Hawthorne"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20author%20of%20the%20novel%20'Brave%20New%20World'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Aldous%20Huxley",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ray%20Bradbury",
        "George%20Orwell",
        "Kurt%20Vonnegut"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20author%20wrote%20the%20play%20'Romeo%20and%20Juliet'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "William%20Shakespeare",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Christopher%20Marlowe",
        "Thomas%20Middleton",
        "Ben%20Jonson"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Language and Literature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20wrote%20the%20novel%20'The%20Great%20Gatsby'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "F.%20Scott%20Fitzgerald",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ernest%20Hemingway",
        "John%20Steinbeck",
        "Sinclair%20Lewis"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
